trustradius.com 2014-07-01

# Privacy Policy | TrustRadius

**YOU ARE USING A BETA VERSION OF OUR WEBSITE. WE WILL RETAIN ANY INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU DURING THE BETA PERIOD. WE MAY CHANGE OUR PRIVACY POLICY BEFORE OUR FINAL LAUNCH.**

TrustRadius (“TrustRadius” or “we”) values your privacy. At our website, https://secure.trustradius.com (the “Site”), we provide a social information sharing network for business professionals. In this Privacy Policy (“Policy”), we describe how we collect, use, and disclose information that we obtain from you when you visit our Site and use our products and services (“Services”).

By visiting the Site, or using any of our Services, you agree that your personal information will be handled as described in this Policy. Your use of our Site or Services, and any dispute over privacy, is subject to this Policy and our Terms and Conditions, including its applicable limitations on damages and the resolution of disputes. TrustRadius's Terms and Conditions are incorporated by reference into this Policy.

  * What Information Do We Collect About You and Why?
  * Information We Collect Directly From You
  * Information that We Collect About You from LinkedIn
  * Information We Collect Automatically
  * How We Use Your Information
  * How We Share Your Information
  * Our Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms
  * Third Party Analytics
  * Third-Party Links
  * User Generated Content
  * Security of My Personal Information
  * Access To My Personal Information
  * What Choices Do I Have Regarding Use of My Personal Information?
  * Children Under 13
  * Contact Us
  * Changes to this Policy

What Information Do We Collect About You and Why?
    We may collect information about you directly from you and from third parties, as well as automatically through your use of our Site or Services.
Information We Collect Directly From You.
    We will collect information directly from you when you interact with certain portions of our Site and/or contact us. Specifically, if you would like to join our Site and have full access to reviews, you are required to register with us. We will collect the following information during registration: your name, email address, employer, job title, and address. We also require you to connect your account with your current LinkedIn account. As part of your user profile, you may (but are not required) to submit additional information, including, for example, your picture, a “headline” describing you, job type, and department. Registered users maintain an anonymous profile which does not include name, job title or company as well as a named profile which does include that information. Registered users control which version of their profile is visible to other site members through their profile settings page.
    We require you to link your account with your LinkedIn profile and to log into our Site using your LinkedIn credentials. We require you to allow us this access to your LinkedIn acccount:

  * We may read your full profile and email address.
  * We may have access to your connections as necessary to make available your profile to your 1st degree connections should you choose that option.
  * We may post network updates and write messages to other users on your behalf with your approval.

We store some information that we receive from LinkedIn with other information that we collect from you with your approval. LinkedIn controls the information that it collects from you. For information about how LinkedIn may use and disclose your information, including any information you make public, please consult its privacy policy. We have no control over how any third party site uses or discloses the personal information it collects about you.
Information We Collect Automatically.
    We may automatically collect the following information about your use of our Site or Services through cookies, web beacons, and other technologies: your browser type and operating system; web pages you view; links you click; your IP address; the length of time you visit our Site and or use our Services; and the referring webpage that led you to our Site. Please see the discussion below entitled “Our Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms” for additional Information.
How We Use Your Information
    We use the information that we gather about you for the following purposes:

  * To provide our Services to you, to communicate with you about your use of our Services, to respond to your inquiries, to fulfill your orders, and for other customer service purposes, which may include communicating with you via email
  * To tailor the content and information that we may send or display to you, personalized help and instructions, and to otherwise personalize your experiences while using the Site or our Services
  * For customer loyalty programs
  * For marketing and promotional purposes. For example, we may use your information, such as your email address, to send you news and newsletters, special offers, and promotions, or to otherwise contact you about products or information we think may interest you. We also may use the information that we learn about you to assist us in advertising our Services on third party websites.
  * We may present information to you about your LinkedIn connections or suggest reaching out to your connections or other people you may know; we do not, however, contact your connections directly (unless they independently are members of our Site)
  * To better understand how users access and use our Site and Services, both on an aggregated and individualized basis, to improve our Site and Services and respond to user desires and preferences, and for other research and analytical purposes

    We do not share your personal information with third parties for their own marketing purposes. We may share the information that we collect about you, including personally identifiable information (collectively, “information”), as follows:

  * TrustRadius Users. Registered users may control certain privacy settings on our Site. As a default, your full profile will be available to all of your LinkedIn 1st Degree Connections. You may change this setting to provide more or less visibility by logging into your account and choosing your preferred privacy setting. All visitors to our Site will be able to see the size and industry of your company and your job type and department (should you choose to provide this information).
  * Service Providers. We may disclose the information we collect from you to third party vendors, service providers, contractors or agents who perform functions on our behalf. These entities assist us with maintaining our Site and our Services, our marketing efforts, and for other purposes.

We also may share your information with the following persons and for the following purposes:
  * Business Transfers. If we are acquired by or merged with another company, if substantially all of our assets are transferred to another company, or as part of a bankruptcy proceeding, we may transfer the information we have collected from you to the other company.
  * In Response to Legal Process. We also may disclose the information we collect from you in order to comply with the law, a judicial proceeding, court order, or other legal process, such as in response to a court order or a subpoena.
  * To Protect Us and Others. We also may disclose the information we collect from you where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Service or this Policy, or as evidence in litigation in which we are involved.
  * Aggregate and De-Identified Information. We may share aggregate or de-identified information about you with third parties for marketing, advertising, research or similar purposes.

Our Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms
    We use cookies and other tracking mechanisms to track information about your use of our Site or Services. We combine this information with other personal information we collect about you to develop a more complete profile about you and to improve your experience on our Site. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser for record-keeping purposes. Some cookies allow us to make it easier for you to navigate our Site and Services, while others are used to enable a faster log-in process or to allow us to track your activities at our Site and Service. There are two types of cookies: session and persistent cookies. We also allow third parties to place cookies on our Site for analytical purposes.

  *  **Session Cookies.** Session cookies exist only during an online session. They disappear from your computer when you close your browser or turn off your computer. We use session cookies to allow our systems to uniquely identify you during a session or while you are logged into the Site. This allows us to facilitate your identity and improve your experience as you move through our Site.
  *  **Persistent cookies.** Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you have closed your browser or turned off your computer. We use persistent cookies to enable you for certain log in purposes as well as to track aggregate and statistical information about user activity.
  *  **Third Party Cookies.** We may also engage third parties to track and analyze Site data. We use the data collected by such third parties to help us administer and improve the quality of the Site and to analyze Site usage. Such third parties may combine the information that we provide about you with other information that they have collected. This Policy does not cover such third parties' use of the data.

Disabling Cookies. Our Site will not function properly without cookies enabled. At minimum, session cookies must be allowed in order to preserve your identity as you navigate the site. If you wish, you can logoff from the site once you are done and then delete any persistent cookies that remain.

Local Storage Objects. We and our third party service providers may use Flash Local Storage Objects (“Flash LSOs”) to store your Site preferences, to personalize your visit or to display content based upon what you view on our Site. Flash LSOs are different from browser cookies because of the amount and type of data stored. In addition, you cannot control, delete or disable the acceptance of Flash LSOs through your browser. For more information on Flash LSOs, or to learn how to manage your settings for Flash cookies, go to the Adobe Flash Player Help Page, choose “Global Storage Settings Panel” and follow the instructions. To see the Flash LSOs currently on your computer, choose “Website Storage Settings Panel” and follow the instructions to review and, if you choose, to delete any specific Flash LSO.

Web Beacons, Pixel Tags and Other Technologies. We use web beacons, such as clear GIFs, web bugs or pixel tags, which are tiny graphics with a unique identifier similar in function to cookies. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on your computer's hard drive, clear GIFs are embedded invisibly on web pages. We may use clear GIFs in connection with our Site to, among other things, track the activities of website visitors, help us manage content, and compile statistics about website usage. We and our third party service providers also use clear GIFs in HTML e-mails to our customers, to help us track e-mail response rates, measure the success of our marketing campaigns, identify when our e-mails are viewed and track whether our e-mails are forwarded.

Third Party Analytics.
    We use automated devices and applications, such as Google Analytics and KissMetrics to evaluate usage of our Site. We also may use other analytic means to evaluate our Services. We use these tools to help us improve our Services, performance and user experiences. We do not share your personal information with these third parties.
Third-Party Links
    Our Site and Services may contain links to third-party websites. For example, occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our Site. These third parties have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of those linked sites, including their information practices.
User Generated Content
    Our Site is a forum for users to share their experience with various products and services. To this end, we invite registered users to post reviews on our Site. Please note, however, that if you post reviews to our Site, then all of the information that you post will be attributed to you. Your full identity will be available to all of your 1st Degree LinkedIn connections unless you change your privacy settings. Please also note certain portions of your identity (the size and industry of the company you work for and your job type and department should you choose to provide it) will be available to all members of our Site. If you post your own content on our Site or Services, your posting may become public and we are cannot prevent such information from being used in a manner that may violate this Policy, the law, or your personal privacy. You are responsible for the accuracy of any information contained in your postings.
Security of My Personal Information
    We have implemented commercially reasonable precautions to protect the information we collect from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Please be aware that despite our best efforts, no data security measures can guarantee 100% security.
    You should take steps to protect against unauthorized access to your password, phone, and computer by, among other things, signing off after using a shared computer, choosing a robust password that nobody else knows or can easily guess, and keeping your log-in and password private. We are not responsible for any lost, stolen, or compromised passwords or for any activity on your account via unauthorized password activity.
Access to My Personal Information
    You may log into your account at any time to update your profile information. Please note that copies of information that you have updated, modified or deleted may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of the Site for a period of time.
What Choices Do I Have Regarding Use of My Personal Information?
    We may send periodic promotional emails to you. You may opt-out of such communications by following the opt-out instructions contained in the e-mail. Please note that it may take up to 10 business days for us to process opt-out requests. If you opt-out of receiving emails about recommendations or other information we think may interest you, we may still send you e-mails about your account or any Services you have requested or received from us.
Children Under 13
    Our Services are not designed for children under 13. If we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we will delete such information from our systems.
Terms and Conditions
    Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our Site.
Contact Us
    If you have questions about the privacy aspects of our Services or would like to make a complaint, please contact us at [support@trustradius.com.](mailto:support@trustradius.com)
Changes to this Policy
    This Policy is current as of the Effective Date set forth above. We may change this Policy from time to time, so please be sure to check back periodically. We will post any changes to this Policy on our Site. If we make any changes to this Policy that materially affect our practices with regard to the personal information we have previously collected from you, we will endeavor to provide you with notice in advance of such change by highlighting the change on our Site, or sending an email to registered users at the last address of record.
